tipnut.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy : TipNut.com

**No Spam Policy**

TipNut.com will not sell your email address to a third party. At no time is personal information collected without explicit consent.

Email subscriptions are managed and delivered by [Google’s Feedburner Service](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Subscribers and users of the Feedburner service are subject to Google’s terms and privacy policies, you can review their [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) and [TOS](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/) before subscribing by email. Tipnut.com is not responsible or liable for the actions, service failures, security measures or policies and procedures of Feedburner.com.

 **Information Logged**

TipNut.com examines log files to analyze trends, see where visitors go in the site, and gather broad general information. Your IP address may be used to help diagnose problems with the host server and to administer this website. This helps improve TipNut.com to meet visitors interests, and promote it more effectively. TipNut.com does not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information. For the majority of the site, the IP is simply stored for security purposes, such as a DOS attack. In cases of fraudulent, harmful or illegal activity (hacking, spamming, DOS attacks, etc.), TipNut.com may share this information with authorities.

Tipnut.com uses the Google Custom Search Engine to provide search support for visitors as well as Google Analytics for traffic stats and monitoring. Google’s privacy policy can be viewed here: [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

TipNut.com may display ads or link to outside advertisers on this site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookie information is stored by the ad company, TipNut.com does not have access to this information. TipNut.com has no control over or access to cookies and tracking methods used by other sites. Cookies are used on TipNut.com for login purposes and may also be used for on site features such as voting, special polls, traffic analysis and logging, etc.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

Tipnut.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

We have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick and its business partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick’s privacy policy at [ValueClick](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/legal/privacy/display-member).

TipNut.com contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. When you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the third parties’ privacy policies. While TipNut.com supports the protection of privacy on the Internet, TipNut.com cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any web site.

 **Security**

This website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. The web hosting company serving TipNut.com has access to all logs and data contained within TipNut.com.

If you need any clarification or further details on any part of this policy, please [contact me](http://tipnut.com/contact/).
